Fauzi Fadhlurrohman

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

CONTACT

Address Jl. Kopo Cirangrang, Kota Bandung, Jawa Barat

Phone 082262311986

Email Fauzi190198@gmail.com

SOCIAL



QUALIFICATIONS

Information System
State Polytechnic of
Subang
2017 - 2020

INTERESTS

Technology Problem Solving Music

SUMMARY

I am a person who is challenged by new things. That really supports me as a software engineer. Starting from wordpress developer until now to be a full-stack developer. But I usually dabble in the backend a lot more. I've had a lot of experience in making projects both from the office and as a freelancer.

ACHIEVEMENT

- 2017 | Best Student Odd Period 2017/2018
- 2018 | Best Student Odd Period 2018/2019
- 2019 | Software Development Fundamentals by Microsoft
- 2019 | MAPRES II Informatics Management
- 2019 | 3rd Winner of the National Essay Competition of IEC
- 2019 | Java English Competition semi-finalist Essay Category
- 2020 | Database Administration Fundamentals by Microsoft
- 2020 | Facebook Digital Enterpreunership by Kominfo
- 2020 | Third best graduate in Information System
- 2021 | Become a Front-End Developer Expert by Dicoding
- 2021 | Practical DevOps with the IBM Cloud by Dicoding
- 2021 | Learn Flutter Application Fundamentals by Dicoding
- 2021 | Facilitator Become a front-end web developer expert by Dicoding
- 2021 | Red Hat OpenShift I: Containers & Kubernetes by Red Hat
- 2021 | Architecting on AWS by Dicoding

ORGANIZATION

- 2017 2018 | Member of TIM Fight FKMPI
- 2017 2018 | Member of PASMA POLSUB
- 2017 2020 | Member of Himpunan Mahasiswa Manajemen Informatika POLSUB
- 2017 2018 | Member of Majelis Permusyawaratan Mahasiswa POLSUB
- 2018 2019 | Leader of English Students Alliance POLSUB

EXPERIENCE

Vortex Store | Freelancer Web Developer 2017 – present

I started a small business before I went to college. The business is called the Vortex Store, which is a web creation service. Initially I created a web using wordpress, but over time I started using frameworks like Codeigniter, laravel, and even flutter.

PT. Len Industri (Persero) | Web Developer (Internship)

September 2019 – January 2020

When I was in college, I had the opportunity to do an internship at a state-owned company called PT. Len Industri (Persero). There I was assigned to develop a system that is useful for managing student data or students doing internships there. The system is called SI-PRAKERIN. The system was created using the PHP programming language and the Codeigniter framework. I developed several features for printing participant cards and fixing the remaining bugs.

PT. Len Industri (Persero) | Site Manager

October 2020 – December 2020

Before I graduated, I applied again to the company where I had an internship. And I was accepted as a site manager to be assigned to a city called Ketapang which is located in the province of West Kalimantan. There I took care of a project from the Ministry of Energy and Mineral Resources, namely the electric street lighting project. I coordinated with the local government to ask for a location survey permit, location data collection, and installation of electric street lighting.

PT. Lapi Divusi | Fullstack Developer

December 2020 - present

PT. Lapi Divusi is a technology company engaged in services and consulting. I work in the Critical Information System. Here I am developing a web project and a mobile application. Starting from developing the frontend, the backend also develops the REST API as a tool for system communication. One of the projects that I have developed is an information system for new student admissions from Parahyangan University.

PROJECT OVERVIEW

PTU Web Contractor

create a landing page for a contracting company located in the Karawang area. This website uses wordpress.

Jepara Furniture Web 2017

In the same year I got a landing page project also to display furniture products in the Jepara area.

Cibeusi Tourism Web 2018

Cibeusi pariwasata web is a web to market tourism and culture in Cibeusi village, Subang, West Java. This web is also a medium for ticket sales for Cibeusi tourism which was built using the Codeigniter 3 framework. This website was created in the framework of village grants with the Subang State

polytechnic.

PT Guna Cahaya Teknik 2019

I got a project from my lecturer, which is to create a company landing page using wordpress. In addition, I also take care of SEO on the web so that it is easier for the google search engine to recognize.

Linumuda 2019

Linimuda is a community website. In addition, the timeline is also a web media for information about life, finance and even careers. This website is made using wordpress.

BDR Polsub 2020

In early 2020 when the pandemic began to enter Indonesia, it prompted various agencies to work from home. This makes one of the integrated service units on my campus to create an attendance system and monitoring for lecturers and staff on my campus. I got an offer to contribute to the system. This system is built using codeigniter framework and mysql database.